# NATHALIE GUSTAFSSON

#### FRONT-END DEVELOPER

#### CONTACT

+46-705621107

■ nath.gustafsson@gmail.com

Gothenburg

mathaliegustafsson.netlify.app

#### **PROFILE**

Front-end developer with experience from start-up, and a background in service and customer relations. During my education, I have built a strong foundation in web development with technologies such as Vue, React and TypeScript. I am driven by the desire to grow in both Frontend and Backend development and always strive to improve my skills.

#### **EDUCATION**

### 2024-2024 HÖGSKOLAN KRISTIANSTAD

• Interaktionsdesign, 7,5hp

## 2022-2024

MEDIEINSTITUTET GÖTEBORG
Higher Vocational Education Diploma

• Front End Developer

#### SKILLS

#### **FRONT-END**

HTML, CSS, SCSS, React.js, Vue.js, JavaScript, TypeScript, MUI, Styled Components

#### **BACK-END**

MongoDB, Mongoose, Node.js, Express.js, Firebase

#### **OTHER**

React-Native, Expo, XCode, Redux, BigCommerce, Stencil, Jest, Git, GitHub, Bitbucket, Figma

#### LANGUAGES

• Swedish: Fluent

English: Fluent

#### LINKS

GitHub

in LinkedIn

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Flourish Feedback | Gothenburg JAN 2024 - NOV 2024 Front End Developer INTERNSHIP → EMPLOYMENT

- Developed new functionality and interface design using Vue, SCSS, and JavaScript.
- Collaborated with UX designer to develop and implement design solutions to improve user experience.
- Contributed ideas for new features and improvements, several of which were implemented in the product, enhancing both usability and functionality.
- Created documentation and flowcharts to support the development team and streamline workflows.

# Wallmander CO | Mölndal

Front End Developer

SEP 2023 - NOV 2023 INTERNSHIP

- Developed and customized themes for BigCommerce using its theme engine, Stencil. Implemented components for Wallmander's custom theme in BigCommerce.
- Created widgets for BigCommerce with HTML, SCSS, and JSON, based on designs in Figma, to meet specific customer requirements.
- Carried out functionality improvements and implemented new features on clients' websites according to their requests and needs.

#### WILLYS AB | Vänersborg

NOV 2018 - SEP 2022

Checkout Supervisor & Assistant Team Leader

- Managed invoices and performed cash reporting to ensure accurate and efficient handling of the store's finances.
- Worked in various areas of the store, as well as the service desk and postal agency, to meet customer needs and maintain a high level of service.
- Adjusted schedules as needed to ensure efficient staffing and smooth workflows.
- Responsible for the operations at the checkout line, quickly and effectively handling issues to provide a positive customer experience.